mailpro.com 2019-02-05

# Privacy Policy and GDPR Compliance of Mailpro

## How we handle you private data?

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personal Data is being used online. Personal Data is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information in accordance with our website and software.  
Since 25 may 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is applying, it includes rules and rights on giving privacy information to you.

## What personal data do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

## When do we collect data?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, Use Live Chat, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.

## How do we use your data?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions and to generate invoices.
  * To send periodic emails regarding our software and application improvements.
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

## How do we protect your data?

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

  We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

  All credit card transactions are processed through our gateway provider, Datatrans AG, Swiss Corporation complying with PCI Standards and are not stored or processed on our servers.

## Where and how long do we store your data?

Your personal data and your application data are stored in our Datacenter in Switzerland, Geneva. The data are kept active as long as you keep a commercial relation with us. If you close your account (in My Account section of our Software) we will erase the data giving a time of 45 to 60 days. We will keep your invoices information for accounting purposes.

## What rights do you have on your personal data?

According to EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), you have the following rights:

Your Rights | How to use them  
---|---  
Right of Access    
Right to Rectification :  
Right to Erasure ("Right to be Forgotten") | You can access your data from our software in the “My Account” area. In this area, you can modify and delete your data by closing your account.  
Right to Restriction of Processing  
  | You can for example keep your account but unsubscribe to our newsletter or other services we provide  
Notification Obligation Regarding Rectification or Erasure of Personal Data or Restriction of Processing | We will send you an email if we modify or delete your data  
Right to Data Portability  
  | In our software, all data can be exported in standard format like XLS, XLXS, CSV  
Right to Object  
  | You have the right and freedom to apply this right by closing your account. We will not process your personal data anymore.  

## What kind of Cookies do we use?

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

  We use cookies to: 

  * Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

  If you turn cookies off, it won't affect the user's experience.

## Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Data unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.

  However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  **Third-party links**

  We may include third-party links on our website such as social media links or other websites links. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

  **Google**

  Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

  We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

  Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

  We have implemented the following: 

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

  Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

  **AdRoll**

  _If you browse  our website, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with mailpro.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number.  _  
**Privacy policy & opt out options: **<https://www.adroll.com/about/privacy>

  _**CloudFlare**_

  _Cookies can be added by the content delivery network (CDN) we use, CloudFlare. We use a CDN to prevent DDoS attacks as well as using caching web content for faster delivery. These cookies are assigned and used only by CloudFlare according to their cookie policy:_<https://www.cloudflare.com/cookie-policy/>

  _**Zendesk**_

  _We use Zendesk’s Support Widget, a Zendesk Inc. Customer Service Platform to process customer inquiries. Information such as last name, first name, telephone number, and email address is recorded on our website in order to answer your questions._

  _For more information about Zendesk’s data processing, see Zendesk’s Privacy Policy at_<https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy> _._

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the US to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

  According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

  You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes: 

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

Can change your personal information: 

  * By logging in to your software and choosing “My Account”
  * By sending us a email to support

## How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

## Data breach Notification (Fair Information Practices)

The data breach notification is part of corporation Data Controllers and Data Processors duties collecting EU personal data, also known in US Law as Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

  In order to be in line with the law we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

  We will notify you via email and via in-app notification, as well as our supervisory authority within 72 hours.

  We also agree to the individual redress principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by Data Processors.

## Contact

For further information about our Privacy Data Policy, send us an email to [legal@maxony.com](mailto:legal@maxony.com) or write to :

  **Maxony Group**  
Impasse Champ-Colin 6  
1260 Nyon  
Switzerland
